[ED.
I love you, Team President.
Ew.
That's why you know everything, Mr. Bread.
You must really like him, don't you, Mr. President?
I love you.
Maybe I really do.
Duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck duck.
Duckin' duckin' cuddly cuddly
Uh...
When I saw the aiki
Mr. Sukura was crying too.
Heh heh heh heh.
You were watching the spring from the outdoor hot spring
Mr. Sakamoto was dancing outside with me.
Ha-ha-ha!
Hi, I'm Yomi-kun, who grew up in Stardash's Vigilant Hands!
Let's have a quick word with today's guest!
This is our idol!
I'm Team President, Dragon's Blue Sakurano!
Nice to meet you!
Ms. Sakurano, it's been a while, hasn't it?
Has it been a while?
I got a little dressed up today. How do you like it?
Oh, that's right.
Is Tricco a Tori?
There's a lot of fluffy stuff here.
There's a bath yuzu-ness to this fluff.
I think she'll like it. Yuzuki seems to like it.
Devil.
I tried to make it a little cute
It's cute.
Thank you very much!
So, only 2 months left in 2023!
So fast!
It's early, isn't it?
How was it? This past year?
Yes, it was.
But the big thing was...
I was allowed to speak out at my one-man shows.
I think it was the biggest thing.
Orca-sama in summer
At the OrcaLive at Nagoya Castle, you were allowed to speak out.
Yes, I took off my mask so I could see everyone's face.
I think it's been a year where I've been able to live a little bit like I used to.
I think it's been a year that I've been able to live a little bit like before.
Team Orca's live show is like that, isn't it?
You and the three of them work together to create a live performance.
It's that kind of live show, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
It seems like you've had a lot of visitors.
Yes, I love Team Shachi.
Who's your favorite? Do you have a favorite?
Oh, I see.
I've been in Stargast for a long time, so it's hard for me to say.
If I had to pick one, I'd say Akimoto-san.
Well, what do you think of her?
The way she always smiles and is so cute.Something about the way she's always smiling and cute.
Oh, but can I just say something here about why Akimoto-san smiles all the time?
I don't think we need to talk about that.
Actually, there is a secret.
Yes.
Normally, people breathe through their noses when they do this.
But Akimoto-san breathes through his mouth like this.
There is an urban legend that he can't breathe through his nose because of rhinitis, so his mouth is open all the time.
Please stop it!
Are you saying that Akimoto-san has always been a mouth breather?
Yes, I do.
She's cute in that way too.
What?
So...
Oh, last time in Osaka.
I was in Osaka last time.
And Kazuhiko Ito,
and Kazuhiko Ito, in Osaka the other day.
Yes, we did. This is the third time we have done it.
The first time was a live performance in Taiwan,
The second time was the Corona Disaster,
The second time was the Corona Disaster, so we did a localism online field day,
We did that.
Yes, we did. And the third time, we finally performed in Japan, in Osaka.
So it was Osaka.
So all three groups are performing locally, where none of them belong.
That's right. The first one was in Taiwan,
Each of us is a local,
So, we are all local, I'm not going to stop somewhere,
Someone else's because it's still a home.
Oh, unfair.
I see. That's what I thought,
But if you do it in Tokyo, it's different.
It's local, isn't it?
That's right. That's why we decided to go to Osaka.
That makes sense.
Yes, that makes sense.